Please give it your all.
尻尽きらしてください
Inka-chan, are you okay?
イ ンカちゃん、いい?
When it comes to filming, there are more moms.
撮影だと、ママが増すと
Is that so?
そうなの?
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょう?
Mom, it's my first time.
ママ、初めて
Stop it.
やめて
That's an experience too.
それも経験だね
experience.
経験
Because it's okay.
大丈夫だから
Mom, can you do it?
お母さん、できちゃう?
ERROR
できちゃうかな?
first time?
初めて?
first time.
初めて
ERROR
これ、初めてだね
Can I do it like this?
こうやってあげる?
Try it like this
こうやってみ
Good morning.
よう
good?
いい?
By yourself.
自 分で
That's tough, Inca-chan.
きついよ、インカちゃん
Let me show you the camera.
カメラ見せてあげてね
tight.
きつい
Look!
見て ごらん
It's okay to take it slow.
ゆっくりでいいよ
Inka-chan is amazing.
インカちゃん、すごいね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Will it go down a bit?
もうちょっと下がる?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Is it a Y-shape?
Y字だっけ?
ERROR
Y字で
soft.
柔らかい
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's just a blink of an eye.
ひとふたになっちゃったね
It's the last time.
最後さ
It worked, right?
効果も立ったでしょ?
This too.
これもさ
Because this is a promise.
こういうのの約束だから
ERROR
最後ね
Chinko, can you please make me feel better?
ちんこ、ちょっと機嫌にしてくれる?
Your face is dirty.
汚れたね、お顔ね
ERROR
重大だからさ
It's sinking in, kind of.
しみ込んでるよ、なんか
Thank you.
ありがとね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Let's take another photo.
また撮影しようね
it was fun?
楽しかった?
It was a good memory.
いい思い出になったね
Now Inka-chan is also an AV actress.
これで インカちゃんもAV女優です
She's a naughty actress.
イッチな女優さんです
Finally, yes.
最後、はい
appear?
見える?
ERROR
視聴者にどうぞ
Thank you for watching until the end.
最後まで見てくれて ありがとうございました
Looks like an actress.
女優さんっぽいね
Thank you.
ありがとね
bye bye.
バイバイ